

I have been acquiring a good set of abilities through my journey as a Front End Developer and I always find a way in order to reach the desired outcomes. From my experience I know the importance of keeping ourselves learning new things, and for my fortune, I enjoy to discover new things and applying them in order to extract the maximum value as posible in order to provide better solutions to problems.

### **CONTACT DATA**

#### Phone number:

+584120318685

## Email:

yosefleanb@gmail.com

#### Portfolio:

www.yosefblandin.vercel.app

#### Github:

www.github.com/YosefBlandin

#### Platzi:

www.platzi.com/p/YosefBlandin

## LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/yosef-blandin-a587241b0

# FRONT END DEVELOPER

## **Yosef Enmanuel Blandin Rios**

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER AT TURPIAL DEVELOPMENT

Nov 2021 - Present

- Built many responsive landing pages and forms using React and Formik.
- Managed the state of the client's web through Redux in order to improve the accesibility of data between components.
- Created a medicine search page using React and made filters which presents the data according to the users' selection.
- Worked with a team and had meetings with English speakers clients.

## FRONT END DEVELOPER AT WINGOO

July 2021 - Feb 2022

- Created landing pages, forms and sidebars using slim template, object oriented programming and sass.
- Lead the migration of the project from Ruby on Rails to Next and worked on standardize all the project using Husky, ESlint, prettier and Typescript.

## FRONT END DEVELOPER AT ZUMETRICS

May 2021 - July 2021

- Responsible of implementing the authentication process using Autho.
- Developed dynamic dashboards, connected APIs, and integrated Epayco as a payment method using Next.
- Learned how to work under agile methodologies, team work and good developing practices on React.

#### **EDUCATION**

- 2022, Harvard, Introduction to Computer Science CS50
- 2020 Platzi courses and self-taught

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

**Languages:** Spanish as a matter language and English B2 according to the EF SET test..